Thank you.
Hey, I got a bad feeling abou-
If it's come to this...
Then, I have no
choice but to get on
board with what
she wants us to do.
Well, there's new regulations on being a hero.
"We're the true heroes..."
That's what it says.
Our heroes are real in this city!
That's my...
...own mission!!
This true hero is a big success!
His name is...
Hyakutoban!
His strength of heart has
stunned even the Dogengers!
YOU'RE UNDER ARRESTTTTT!
Hey, wait a second! You didn't
say we were going that fast!
He keeps apprehending more members
of the Secret Society of Darkness!
Apologies for the trouble!
It's all over...
I'm just doing my duty the best I can.
And as for this officer's popularity?
It's completely flipped! Thanks to this hero's activities...
- Wow, that's amazing!
- You really did it!
This is so embarrassing...
I can't believe they cut my ratings from that poll!
Something smells fishy about all of this...
True enough. But...
That's so cool!
-Congratulations!
-Congrats!
I-It's all thanks to you guys!
Well, still...
Anyone would lose when the competition is putting away violent criminals.
Huh? It feels like someone's missing...
Now that you mention it...
Huuuuuuaaaangh...
KitaQman! Are you alright?
I'm not... definitely not!
My...
My phone... no matter where I look...
Oh my gas...
Nah.
Why don't you try calling it?
Big bro?
SP110-Px was developed by the police department to perform special operations.
Its name: Special Agent Hyakutoban!
I feel lonely...
These will do!
Huh?
Sure enough,
it's not the same.
What do we do?!
All we could-
Leave it to me.
Yuz-yuz-chan!
Here ya go! This
what you wanted?
I don't want it!
Wait! Yuz-yu-
Stop worrying about her, what about the Boss!
I gotta follow my gut as a screenwriter this time!
Hello?
Ah. This is Maid Butler?
KitaQman Metal!
Maid Goooat!
If you've got a problem with that, why don't you come over and fight us?
And why don't you bring your new car over here?
I'll destroy it with my bare hands!
I'll bring some paper scraps for
you to chew on, Gran Maid.
OH, THAT'S IT!!!
This is our course of action?
Oh, Maid Butler gets really upset
when someone compares them to a goat.
This, for your fever.
I leave the rest...
Alright! It's been awhile...
Let's all get along,
and go arrest someone!
ALRIGHT!
We're off.
-We'll be back!
-We will be back!
I'll be baaaack~
Let's go!
Shiraishi.
Yes?
You've got a meeting.
Huh?
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN DOING TO MY CREATION?!
UUEAAAAAAAH!
Aww, man! Look how beat up it is!
Time for an inspection.
Huh?
-W-w-wha-
-This way.
Well.
Uh, what am I supposed to do?
Give directions.
...Roger.
How'd it even get this damaged?
Aww, man!
Now then...
I have some questions.
The havoc at the Oshikawa estate...
Tell me what happened.
I have the right to remain silent.
Is that so?
How you doing over there?
Of course! I'm doing fine.
What do you think?
I think a design that relies on the human body...
...is a complete and utter mistake!
Is that any way for a younger brother to talk?
I expect an older brother to make better design choices.
Nooo.
My own behavior algorithm...
Noooo.
The artificial intelligence I installed into Yuz-...
"The one I designed...
...was much better!", huh?!
It... it can't be...
R...
Remaining silent...
You better start talking.
Because I'm out of patience.
This feeling...
I'VE BECOME A POLICE OFFICER!
It's been a while, huh?
Even though so much has happened...
From here on out, I'm still...
WHAAAAAAEEEUEUUUUGGGGAAAAAUGH
W-w-w-what do I do?!
Now...
When I can't become Hyakutoban!
Huh?
Hey, Shiraishi.
Yes?
I have a problem.
My brother... created...
Yes. I created it!
Your work is passable.
Because I'm different from you.
A younger brother who's better
than me doesn't exist!
I exist right here, right now!
First off, let's take a look at your project.
Anyway, that's...
The frame and motor don't seem to be compatible.
It's because you only use the cheap plastic DC motors!
You two get ahold of-
It's always...
Been this way.
Big bro!
Take a look!
-Huh?
-My little brother...
Was always better at building things than I was.
But I always...
Big bro?
That's nothing to be proud of.
I could never admit it.
I'm older than you!
I'm your older brother!
But...
I knew.
I was beaten out...
By my younger brother.
Same goes for me.
Hey.
Where is he?
Same as always.
I'm in a bad mood today.
Same as always!
Of course there are times when he helps me out...
Hey, move over, bro!
Don't get in the way of my job!
You certainly have a way with words.
And I'm always grateful...
But what every older brother should be doing...
Metallic Smash!
Is supporting their younger brother.
Supporting him?
After this...
Can we work to...
...gether?
Well, then.
Hm?
How bothersome.
It seems...
I have but one choice.
Is that so?
So you don't know what you
really want anymore?
Yeah...
I, too...
Hm?
Up to now, it was always...
What's the best way I can live?
What should I do with my life?
I'm always worried, even right now.
But...
I'm won't be lost on it anymore!
I'm kind of a wimp to start with.
It's the fault of my cowardice's that...
...No, it's thanks to my cowardice
that I can become Hyakutoban.
There is nothing I won't do...
to fulfill my duty!
For things like my own mission,
Not if I can stop it!
And no trivial villain...
...or trivial problem...
...gets overlooked by a hero.
What a police officer must do...
You don't need to wonder what to do.
I was already doing it.
No need to fret about it.
Just keep at it with all you've got.
To keep going is vital.
I...
...will protect the galaxy.
Listen here.
Heroes...
They protect the whole universe!
-Yozakura!
-Buster!
My seniors were always behind me, reminding me that there are heroes out there.
That's great.
I've just been failing over and over.
No, no! I'm failed too!
But...
Wow... you really are a hero!
- Now!
-One slash!
Because of the people I can rely on...
You did good.
Don't ever say "your safety" again!
From here on out, I'm counting on you to speak your mind.
And thank  to those who told me what
I was doing wrong, I became who I am.
Every now and then...
Looking back at everything up
to now can't hurt, can it?
"Everything up to now..."
Yup!
If you were to do that,
You might find what it is you want.
Remember...
Got it!
I'm not lost anymore!
Shiraishi, you're awesome!
Not at all.
Giving people directions
is a police officer's job!
You can become a true hero.
Shiraishi?
Keeping everyone safe is my job.
So that's how it is, huh?
I...
Shiraishi?
What's wrong?
Don't cry!
S-sorry! I'm alright!
I'm not done yet.
This isn't a time to be crying!
I'm alright now!
After all, I'm one of these... HUUUUH?!
Bye bye!
HEY, WAIT!
Hey!
What is it you want, Shiraishi?
IT'S YOUR ARREST!!
YOU WON'T GET IT!
I'll remember!
This isn't enough!
- This isn't what I wanted.
- It's not any of these!
Huh? You don't want it...?
I'm going to work.
I'll go too!
Staying home and drinking is fun!!
I've got it!
That'll do it!
That's amazing, little bro!
True, but big bro...
This is one slick machine!
Thanks to you!
I call it the Skeletal Support Actuator!
Wait, what?!
I built an SS Activator, too!
Even the two names are similar.
We must be siblings!
So does Yuz-Yuz have the same abilities?
Oh, not really.
I haven't actually installed mine yet.
Why's that?
Well you see, my gadget...
It makes her go berserk.
She destroyed the entire Oshikawa estate.
I hid the SS Activator...
Under the tatami floor!
Shoot.
- Another loss...
- That's a win.
Thank you, big bro.
Dangit. Let go!
No way I'm letting go.
Do release them to us.
-C'mon.
-Right.
-Huh?
-What are you doing?
Hey, what're you doing?
Hold on a minute!
For your gracious cooperation,
we offer our graditude.
However...
Hm?
-What's that?
"Hero activity"...
- "New regulations"?!
- Whaaat?
From here forwards...
He'll do us the favor...
...of working on his own.
Um so, get this!
I had a talked with Shiraishi!
I think they've lost the ability to distinguish good and evil, but...!!
You really think the police
will let 'em off the hook?
I can't just stop supporting them.
Next time: Only I was Wrong.