I'm baaaack!
My company really is the best!
Huh?
Hey? Hey! Shaberry!?
Hey! C'mon! Shaberry!
How could something like this happen?
Huh?
He left a dying message?
Farewell!
Uh, what's it say...?
“Those are all of this city's backwards compatible...?”
SSA...?
The Skeletal Support Actuator...
It's possible...
This isn't the same kid we've
been dealing with anymore.
Right.
Therefore...
If that's the case...?
Understood.
Shiraishi.
I'll remove it...
Her's...
That is!
I'm not lost anymore!
What's wrong? Don't cry!
I'm alright now!
You know this isn't right.
Yuz-Yuz.
This isn't right!
That thing...
Needs to be taken away.
But... I don't like you, Shiraishi!
If I hadn't layered these so thick,
I could have been in danger!
Huh?
B-boss?
“I'm heading out.”
Yuz-Yuz...
You... need to wake... up.
Hang in there... Shiraishi!
That's an order!
Please wake up!
Come back! You need to come back this time!
Please!
I, too... when I was lost...
I thought it was the end. Just like this!
But...
A true hero...
Saved me!
And even now...
I'm being supported by everyone else!
So... what I have to do as a police officer...
Heh.
I see.
Is to keep giving people directions...
What I... have to do...
Huh?
All this...
It's been a while.
My life flashing before my eyes.
Why?
Hm?
Why did you do all that?
Well...
The best thing I could think to do...
Is give you the thing you want.
Come on.
You got the thing you wanted?
I did.
But...
If I did something bad...
You would always scold me.
Thank you, Shiraishi!
I love you!
No way...
All of this?
Was my....
life......
Yuz-Yuz!
Are you alright?
It'll be alright.
Now..
I... I'm...
...crying.
But...
I don't have the right
mouth parts for it...
No tears, either...
Because I'm just... a thing...
But...
I'm... cry...ing...
Right?
Looks like I did something bad.
Maybe I was wrong.
Ugh, what can I do if I can
only think of lame things to say?
Whatever.
I can't allow anyone
to be more evil than I am.
Yep! And with this, I'll be the
baddest one there is.
Hm. This is a rare pattern.
This is our first time meeting.
But I'm glad!
It's better this way.
With me this powerful you've got no choice but to suck up to me.
Now, officer.
You're under arrest.
I'd like to see you try.
GO ON AND TRY!!!
Mr. Akuta...
Make the arrest.
YOU'RE UNDER ARREEEEEESSST!
It's alright.
Th_his fe_fe_feeli_eling...
Hahaha_Fe_fe_feel_ling_ha...
And you?!
WAAAAAIT!!
Chief Yoriki...
I was useless... but I've changed.
I'm sure... I can fix this!
Really?
Yeah.
Because we're brothers.
They exist...
They exist here!
Villa_lains?
Heroes!
WHE_E_RE?
We...
CAN DO IT!!
ALRIGHT!
Ha...te...na...
S-Stop... stop...
Ag! Ow ow ow!
-Hey, hold on!
I'm supposed to be the hot one!
Hm?
Oh? Oh! That's right.
You, too...
-You filthy...
-You, too...
Right!
Alright, time for training. Hurry, hurry!
Right, sit down, sit down.
Here we go.
We are...
-Dogengers.
-No way...
-Oh, no...
-Waa!
Wha-?
Yay!
Now then, the portable panel!
Here it comes!
There!
AH, IT'S HERE!
-Oh, this is fantastic!
-AWESSSOOME!
W_Whe_Where?!
Where?!
WHERE?!
He's too strong...
Mr. Akuta!
Let's do this together.
I'll support you.
Right!
Are yo_you for re_re_real?
This body's the best.
Got you.
Mr. Akuta!
I'll leave the rest to you.
...Right!
Leave the rest to me...
Ohgaman?!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Now, prepare yourself!
Everyone...
Let's get 'im!
-Alright!
-Okay!
He changed again?!
He may have changed.
But so have we!
You al_all... I'll ta_ake y__you
Thing... people... it doesn't
make a difference!
This entire city...
We'll support everyone!
Tha_at's...
Make the arrest.
YOU'RE UNDER ARRESTTTTTT!!!
ARREEEEEEEEEEEEEEEST!
ARRREEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEST!
ARRRRRREEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEST!
What's.. hap_pening to me?!
- We got him!
-Alright!
We finally did it!
We did it...
Um...
Y'know?
I-I...
Right now I'm...
Smiling a bit?
Is that it?
You got it!
A few days later...
Thank you for all you've done!
- I'm gonna miss you so much!
- But...
It's thanks to all of you I was
able to fulfill my duty as an officer!
Thank you all.
Besides...
I... No.
We'll still be together.
Right!
As the defendants are not human, there is
no way we can try them in a human tribune.
As such, they must be found not guilty.
Secret Society of Darkness Lawyer, Tatsuki Matsumura
There's no way that argument can stand!
Not guilty.
YES!!!
- Your honor!
- From here on out...
Please fight fair.
Right! That'll do it!
Time to dig in!
Yaba Curry! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Delivering to all of mankind, Dogengers: Star Four. Thanks for waiting.
I'm still not a part of it...
Punishment for the damage you caused.
Gehhh! That's a lot.
Don't own swords of firearms.
Don't break things. And don't steal.
Do not do bad things.
That's the path to a normal life.
In short, doing bad things are no good!
THIS IS RIIIIGHT!
20052, 20053, 20054, 20055...
I'LL CHANGE MYSELF!
Where's your partner?
His probation period is over.
You sure need a lot of prodding.
You men...
Well?
Yeah.
Ohgaman's Guide to Smart Dating
Wanna grab a bite?
Victory!
Shiraishi!
U-uh... um...
Uh, y'know? Yeah.
So...
-So...?
So, yeah.
Yuz-Yuz?
Yeah, me.
I'm thinking of leaving the city.
I'm thinking about what I want.
To do that, I need to know a lot of stuff!
So, then...
Uh... yeah, right?
I've got something big to ask you.
Y'know...
Even if we're apart...
Can you always be near me?
Of course!
I'll always be here to support you!
I did it... I did it!
I DID IT!
So!
What's the big question?
What did you have for breakfast?
What do you think?
Surely, true heroes...
...aren't something you turn into.
When going through each ane every day day.
At some point?
We can become heroes together.
Always and truly, thank you!