I'd like...
... to speak to you.
I'd like to tell you something.
Akuta...
I'd like to have a talk.
I've certainly gotten in deep with these people.
I'm starting to think that awaiting Judgment Day
is itself another choice.
I've sewn the seeds of doubt...
At this juncture, I cannot go back.
I should return with what I've stolen, as well.
Or should I...?
SP110-Px was developed by the police department to perform special operations.
Its name: Special Agent Hyakutoban!
I won't run away anymore! I'll never give up!
We'll support each other again and again
I'll protect this metropolis, for the future I want to believe in
Swear to give me the praise I need to grow! Dogengers!
The dream I saw that day will someday come true
Yes, if I find the strength to surpass my days of being timid
To shine brighter than the wimp I knew myself to be
Like a beacon telling me not to forget my mission
Anyone can pretend to be tough, like a stubborn machine
And when we realize that, we can find friends!
There's an APB on you: you are wanted!
Because your dreams are not fictional
I want to be a hero just like you
I won't run away anymore! I'll never give up!
We'll support each other again and again
I'll protect this metropolis, for the future I want to believe in
Swear to give me the praise I need to grow! Dogengers!
Good morning!
Shiraishi!
Ooh, sorry. Sorry.
Um...
You've done well here.
So...
Clearly, the problem...
...is with me. So...
Akuta?
Please reconsider...
...your decision to quit.
Huh?
But, I'm not quitting.
What?
What do we do?
No weaknesses...
Not a single one.
Oh. Good morning.
Hatena!
We deeply apologize for you having to
fight those unbelievably powerful heroes!
Please reconsider your decision to quit!
But... I do not plan to quit?
I have no such intent.
As the new employee, it's only natural I should put myself in stressful situations in order to gain your trust.
Since I have joined this organization, we have had new options at our disposal.
I'd like to leverage these to achieve results.
If any of them would seem useful...
What's this supposed to be?
The reason I joined the police,
like I said earlier...
Out of admiration for the officer who
saved me when I was lost,
I thought " I want to be like that!"
To become a real hero,
I can't afford to be discouraged by something like this.
But...
Shall we continue
this suffering later,
you and I?
Everything I've learned has
changed into worries.
I've started wondering if I can ever become like that...
So, when I said I'd like to talk...
I see.
It's another loss!
Akuta...
Please...
Remove me from my post.
I know I'm the only one who
can become Hyakutouban...
It's my fault I can't properly use its power!
So...
- Please dismiss me from my post.
- Don't ever say that again!
I won't allow it.
-Akuta!
-Shiraishi!
Uh, have one of these.
-But...
-Akuta has changed.
Huh?
Back then, he was way scarier.
They called him "Akuta the Devil."
Officer Akuta.
I'd like to tell you something.
Every one of Akuta's
subordinates eventually quit.
He was, perhaps, just far too strict.
But why he was like that?
It's his business, so I'm sure
he's never told you, but...
Natsuki...
Natsuki!
He lost someone very close to him.
Natsuki?
From that day forward...
Natsuki!
Akuta became the devil.
Since then, he's become prone to jumping to conclusions.
No doubt he thought his attitude
was making you want to quit.
But that...
He always keeps things to himself!
Whenever you're suffering, so is Akuta.
Uh, I am too, of course.
There's a saying, "We may start off different,
"but everyone shares the same suffering..."
So it's not just me...
Everyone else, too...
Well, first off,
Start by working through your own problems.
If you do, you can become a true hero.
I am the chief, after all...
So why not talk to me from time to time?
Thank you, sir.
So, what'll you do next?
Of course!
I'm taking off!
Looks like I've done it again.
But that guy...
Will he come back?
Welcome!
Thanks!
Good luck my guy.
Three?
That'll be eight-hundred yen.
Wait a min- aah!
Get your mittens off me!
Shadow, help!!
Hurry up already!
Ever since you came, Yuz-yuz,
you've been too much to handle!
But...
Do as the child wishes.
What was Shabberyman thinkin'?
Huh?
It's incredible.
Isn't it?
Hey, what's that?
What's this thing used for?
Hey! What'd you come here for?
Oh, right!
I want a scabbard!
A scabbard?
She doesn't mean...
The Heshikiri-Hasebe, from the Sengoku period?!
That!!!
That's...
That's in the Natural History Museum,
not the art gallery.
Huh?
I don't get it.
I'm sayin', this is the wrong place!
It ain't here!
Eh?
Fine, whatever!!
Whaddya think you're doin'?
I don't have what I want!
So,
-It's incredible.
-Isn't it?
I'll just take what other people want!
That's what I was thinking!
Calm down! If the police
or something find us...
For the crime of theft...
...He'll arrest...
-You.
Aah.
I wonder where Mr. Akuta went off to.
I can't even get through to him on radio.
-Huh?
-There's an ongoing incident!
A-A-Akuta?
At the Fukuoka Museum of Art!
Get over here now!
Hurry, please!
Nice shot!
Is that how it is??
It's just like in an arcade...
Are you alright, sir?
- Who are you?
-Ah?!
Thanks for saving me.
Huh? Kireko?
But that would mean...
High School
Class Reunion Tour
Stop right there!
My Lady!
The Greatest in Japan!
But, without Kireko, you
can't transform, right, Mako?
That...
That used to be the case.
UWAAAAAH!
Huh? H-how do you have that?
Well...
She's just so cool when she transforms that it just couldn't bear to be apart from her!
-Hey, Ryoko!
-She never changes.
Good luck!
We're going to be late for the next activity!
That'd make me a little sad.
No need to be sad!
Because we'll always be together from here on out!
That's dangerous...
If you're attacking like this, I won't hold back!
Catch me!
I've never been able to get what I want.
Take this!
What?
Time for me to play rough.
What happened? She was so normal a second ago!
W-w-woah, she's scary...
Really? Because I feel like this is normal for me!
Cut that out!
You've taken things too far!
My Lady!
I got it!
Alright!
Getting in my way again...?
I...
Just want...
Huh?
Mr. Akuta? Mr. Akuta!
Mr. Akuta... Mr. Akuta...
So no one...
Wants this thing?
Eh?
What we want...
Is to protect people!
Then I don't need this.
Bye bye!
W-wait...
-Why?
-Take this!
Are you alright?
Th-thank you!
No problem at all!
Well, then... Let's protect them...
Together!
I'm never forgivin' you, Mako!
Don't worry!
-Make the arrest...
-YOU'RE UNDER ARRREEEEEEST!
Over here! You can't catch me!
Ya arrested me yet?
Arrested me yet?
Make some distance between you!
Right!
Mr. Akuta!
I not going to stop worrying anytime soon but...
I won't hesitate anymore!
Hey, hey~
Now!
Oh, Shadow!
We may be apart right now but we'll be together again in prison!
We'll be out by this afternoon.
Long live the Secret Society of Darkness!
Let go! Get your
mittens off me!
Everyone!
Thank you for all the help!
Not at all!
This is normal for us.
Everyone, we're running late!
We gotta go!
Well, I have to go!
A pleasure meeting you.
M-Mr. Akuta?
Uh...
-I'll be alright. I'll get to a hospital.
-I...
May be your subordinate, but...
Uh...
I don't think it's wrong to
talk about what's worrying you.
So...
If you'd be alright with it...
Until now...
I would never tell anyone anything.
I just couldn't do it.
I was so focused on making everyone do their jobs,
That I couldn't tell them what I wanted to.
But right now...
It seems like you have a reason to talk,
so I'll let you talk.
What do you think things are like right now? When people don't talk to each other?
I don't understand the question.
We've got no one to make us try talking.
In the past...
We used to try because of our bosses.
I would do it too.
But now?
No one says a word.
They're afraid of being criticized for how they feel.
So in the end...
We start criticizing ourselves instead.
It's my fault I can't properly use its power!
You acted like it was your fault.
I did too.
I'm worried that...
You'll start criticizing yourself too much.
- And I can't stand to see you do that to yourself.
-  Mr. Akuta...
From here on out?
I'm counting on you to speak your mind!
Right.
Thanks.
Oh, aren't you one of those Secret Society of Darkness goons everyone's been talking about?
Woo-hoo!
Looks like we've made the city peaceful again.
So it would seem.
So, I decided to congratulate you directly.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Thank you.
Hey, I got a bad feeling abou-
If it's come to this...
Then, I have no choice but to get on board with what she wants us to do.
Do you think you could give me one more chance?
Thanks for your hard day's work
You're an officer protecting the city
Handsome guys love black vinegar
Riding through nature on a trike
I want a gas-fired pizza oven
One more slice! So good! One more slice!
And if you're too fashionable, try interior design!
Thanks for all that you do! We're so grateful
You've arrested all of our troubles
You're an orthodox hero, with willpower like a steel beam!
Your apartment's so popular online
But if it goes too viral, we'll say "gomentaiko"!
Let's take our medicine and sleep for a healthy tomorrow!
And we'll meet again with a smile
We'll protect you! - The Dogengers
Being the boss has been tough lately, huh?
Seems like you've been adjusting well though.
Cut it out.
This time at least.
You know what happened wasn't your fault, right?
If you've got nothing important to discuss, I'll be leaving.
Still distancing yourself from others?
Well, there's new regulations on being a hero.
"We're the true heroes,"
That's what it says.
Hey, everyone!
Yuz-Yuz and Hyakutouban. Their story will be coming to a close soon!
You'll love what the screenwriters did with it.
Next: Pickpocket!
Have you been suffering?