I can't believe I'm losing my entire family!
Hey, um...
What?!
Um, well...
To put it simply...
You can't just take other people's things.
I can't?
Absolutely not!
Is it bad to take other people's things?
Huh?
I guess so.
What happens if I take them?
Well... You'll face divine punishment.
But I don't want divine punishment!
Then I guess you'll just have to buy them!
Buy them?
You can buy things with money.
Ooh, that smells nice!
Then gimme some!
Are you dumb?!
The whole reason we're in trouble is because I don't have any.
Dang it...
Really?
Of course.
Really, really?
Really, really!
Really?!
Give it a rest already!
Score!
I'm heading out!
Ah, kids these days, right?
She's got no sense of right and wrong, riiight?
Isn't that riiiiight?
You've gotta be kidding me!!!
Yay!
I did it! That should be everything.
Let's go!
It's...
GOOOONE!!!
- What's gone?
- What happened?
When he woke up this morning, his belt was gone.
And instead...
There was a stack of money.
But why?
Alright, we should turn this over to forensics.
I haven't left the house yet, so I haven't committed a crime!
So you've resorted to stealing?!
Bro...
In addition...
My swords are also missing.
Why did they take those too?
Well, we need to search for clues first...
Sh-Shiraishi!
Shirai—!
Are you two alright?
I guess this should be expected.
The two of you have been pushing yourselves too hard lately.
Sorry about that. But you don't have to... don't have to worry...!
That one sounded like it hurt...
Oh, my...
What to do now...?
Police Chief For A Day
(Contract renewed daily)
Greetings, it's me. Your bag has been stolen.
Really?!
Now that everyone's here...
Our friends in the Special Operations Division will be taking the day off.
In their place...
We, the Dogengers, will exercise our right to be "Police Chief for the Day."
We'll make them pay!
Let's do it!
What're we gonna do?
Now, let's get the theme song you've been waiting for...
...Staaaaaarted!
- Huh?
- YEAH!!
Yuz-Yuz...
...is totally gonna become mega-popular!
Episode 7:
Dueling
Park looks good!
Why did I have to come too?!
We don't know anything about being police officers.
Where should we go next?
Which way should we go?
Which way?
You want me to decide, don't you...
- STRAIGHT AHEAD!!!
- LET'S GOOO!!!  - Roger that.
HUH—??
This is all wrong.
I don't understand.
What is it I really want?
There you are!!
Hey!
Give it back!
Give what back?
The money, of course! Give it back!
I spent it all and bought this stuff.
Ooh, I see! You bought stuff, all proper!
You did a good job, Yuz-Yuz!
Come over here, I want to make sure you hear me clearly.
YOU'RE DEAD!!
Be quiet!!
Hold it right there!
We're the Dogenpolice!
W-What do I do?
It's just like...
No one move!!
It's just like then!
Is that a crime?
Well he's using a hostage to coerce us, so it would count as dueling, I guess.
In that case... bring him in.
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST!!
Ah, shoot. In that case...
Yuz-Yuz, you look really cute today!
"Your subordinate grows with encouragement!"
Time to put those words to the test!!
Your Subordinate
Your Subordinate Grows With
Your Subordinate Grows With Encouragement!
You're so cute, Yuz-Yuz!
I think we could work well together! What do you think?
Wow, look at how much fun we're having! This is a blast.
Okay, sure!
That should do.
Oh, of course.
Ow-ow-ow! That hurts!
That's enough!
I feel much better!
I think I'm ready to...
Why don't you take it easy today, okay?
Shiraishi.
Yes?
L-Let me ask you something.
Chapter 4: Talk With Your Subordinate!
Why did you join the force?
Oh...
How do I explain it?
Thanks for your hard work, weirdos.
You're all under arrest!!
W-W-W-W-Wait a minute!
One! Two! Three!!
Wrong... weight class...
And the winner... Ex!!
AWESOME!!!!
Or actually...
My baaaad!
But what about me...?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I am!
But um...
R-Referee...
You knocked him out!
What do we do, what do we do? We're in trouble. What do we do?!
What's happening to him?
...its behavior algorithm!
It's the finest that's ever been created!
The Special Operations Suit is...
...moving on its own!!
Wake up, El Brave!
Good morning, you two.
This is my chance.
Oh my goodness!
One of you was slacking off, there.
But which of you is at fault?
We'll just say it's the one in red.
Th-This is bad...
Watch out!
My swords?
And this is for you!
Yoko!
I'm so relieved.
And for you.
None of those were what I really wanted.
Thanks anyway.
I'm so tired...
We're going home, boys!
Huh? But my money...
Wait a minute! Get back here!!
Kids these days, I swear...
Dang it—!!
Now then.
Combine. Set.
Let's go!!
C'mon, lay off!
You all got your stuff back!
And in that case, where's my money?!
Is this who I am now?
When did it all start?
When did I start always relying on others?
Hey there.
That looks heavy.
Let me help you with that.
It's no trouble, really.
Oh...
Please wait a moment.
- Guess it's empty.
- How are we doing today?
Oh, officer. Doing great, thank you.
Let's get you home.
I was full of motivation.
I even got promoted to inspector.
You're great, officer!
But then...
It's time for the meeting.
I'll be right there.
I have a case of violent assault, requesting immediate backup.
Roger that. We'll have to reschedule that meeting.
Understood.
There you are, Inspector, I finally caught up with you.
- Have you found a green wallet? Hey, listen to me!
- Sir, this needs your immediate attention.
Hey, listen to me! It's a green wallet.
Inspector! Inspector Yoriki!
Inspector Yoriki, here's that operations report.
I used to try handling everything myself...
Inspector Yoriki, there's someone for you on the other line.
Inspector?
Inspector, about the meeting.
Could I...
Count on you for that?
Then I started relying on others.
And now here I am...
I've always looked up to the officer who helped me when I was lost.
I thought "That's who I want to be like."
Really?
Where are they now?
I was just a child at the time, so I don't know.
But...
I'm sure that...
He's still out there, being someone's hero.
Take that! You know for all your strength...
There seem to be a lot of cracks forming in this patrol, don'tcha think?
We're no good!
That includes you.
And it includes me!
The person I am right now just isn't enough.
But I'm not leaning on others anymore!
I'm just one person!
And I'm going to do whatever I can!
So I'm leaving this to you!
And what comes next...
...IS ALL ON ME!!
Awesome!!
Give back...
MY BELT—!!
El Brave is back in the ring!!
Special Operations Suit SP110-Px Police Badge Operation Report
Filling out all these reports is actually super stressful.
- Hello?
- How you doing?
- Pardon the intrusion!
- This place is huge!
- Great!
- Hello?
- Where is it?
- Hello? Are you there?
Second drawer from the top.
Got it!
Is this it?
Arrest Warrant Request Form (A)
I found it!!
It's finished!
YORIKI
Yabai Kamen!
Huh? What?!
For taking certain persons hostage and for starting a shootout...
You're under arrest!
Let's finish this!
What's going on?
We can make this work!
I'll give it back! Please forgive me!
Brave Impact!
ELECTRIC BLAST!
BRAVE IMPACT:
BRAVE IMPACT: ELEC
BRAVE IMPACT: ELECTRIC
BRAVE IMPACT: ELECTRIC BL
BRAVE IMPACT: ELECTRIC BLAST
Victory for El Brave!
Awright!
He did it!
Here you go.
- You can leave the rest to us.
- We've got it.
- Cuffs!
- Yeah!
I'm counting on you.
Inspector Yoriki seems to be in a good mood.
What do you think happened?
Uh, d-did something happen?
Nope, nothing of note...
We all worked hard today.
Don't scare me!
You're one to talk!
They're gone...
No...
- Huh?      - What's gone?
- What's he talking about?
Who's gone?
- You've got to be kidding!!
- Are those...?
What is that?
This is something else I bought.
Ta-daaa!
The Idolls are gone!!!
ARRESTED
Thank you for your cooperation.
This isn't really the time for a "Hi everyone!~"
Next Episode
The boss got arrested! What are we gonna do?!
Um, Yuz-Yuz...
Is that what I think it is?!
Next Time: "A Serious Guns And Swords Control Violation".
Episode 8
A Serious Guns And
Swords Control Violation
Do you mean me?
Apparently, Yoriki treated El, Kalibur, and Ex to dinner!