Time to battle, Ohgaman!
Get read-ow!
- Here I go!
- W-wait--
My name is KitaQman!
I've got a million followers!
KitaQ Punch!
It's all over...
Ohga!
Aah! Someone help meee!
My brothers could help me,
but I'm no good—
Even the boss has been arrested.
What're we gonna do with this?
Wait!
No, seriously! Wait, Yuz-Yuz!
At least give those back!
Are those things that you wanted?
Nope.
In that case...
But they're awful fun to play with!
See ya later! Yay!
What do we do?
We have to be the adults in the room here.
Listen, Yuz-Yuz!
You've taken something again.
You gotta give it back to 'em, and quick.
♪ It is truly good for your health,  ♪
♪ so please go take a walk~ ♪
Wait, with me?
Sorry.
- Then I have no choice.
- None?
SP110-Px was developed by the police department to perform special operations.
Its name: Special Agent Hyakutoban!
Sorry for starting off with a scene about something
important you might not understand!
Episode 8:
A Serious Guns And
Swords Control Violation
You okay?
This almost never happens.
Gotta get this.
Hey, cut it out!
I didn't know he could get like this...
I don't think he's kidding around.
...Brother?
I'm heading out.
Oh.
Then, I'll accomp...
THIS TIME...
I'm gonna handle this alone...
Oh, my brother...
Shiraishi. We're gonna join him.
Wow Akuta, you really hurt yourself this time.
Akuta?
Here goes...
Me, too!
I've learned so much!
I'll be alright on my own!
I'm heading out!
Odd guy, but he's got spirit.
My name is Hatena.
While living among people, I wondered...
What are people living? What are they trying to leave behind?
And while pondering such questions,
I happened to enter the employment of
the Secret Society of Darkness.
And now,
I find myself walking a mysterious girl.
Humanity is rife with choice.
But prior to choice must come a task.
And from there, one makes a decision.
Then a new choice arises.
This is surely another
task I must fit in its place.
However...
It's not what I wanted,
but I like it!
Aah, how bothersome.
Both or some?
Um... are you alright?
How could this happen?!
I didn't know those things were
so special to you.
They aren't things!
They're Idolls, Shiraishi!
They spent their precious time with me!
Their precious...
Truly, everything I am...
Is thanks to those girls!
Tanaka...
Helping me through tough times...
Always protecting me...
AND SO!!
I will bring them back, no matter what.
Wow... you really are a hero!
I'm... well, I'm only a junior hero, but...
I feel the same way!
Hyakutoban...
I swear to bring in the culprit.
To where should I next turn?
The path of righteousness...
There will be much sacrifice.
You're Yuz-Yuz, right?
I've heard about you.
Huh?
Thanks!
Please give them back.
Two very serious choices.
These?
Please, come quietly.
Two choices that divide destiny...
Well, uh...
No!
Rookie...
Let's take them back.
Give them back.
Uh...
What am I to do with this choice?
How bothersome.
Suspect in sight!
Bring 'em in!
You're under arrest!!
I can't give you direct help this time.
Don't be reckless.
I'm alright!
Even on my own...
I can do it!
Hey! What's best for the suspect?
Ninjin!
What shall I choose?
Calm down, Shiraishi!
Got it?
Resist any further and...
I'll charge you with obstruction of justice!
We are evenly matched.
What is your plan?
Stand down and come with me!
How about this one?
What's wrong?
The suspect has changed weapons!
What with?
It's alright!
I can do this...
By myself!
Not this, either...
Surely, this won't work either.
Yozakura!
No way...
Which is the correct path?
I myself do not yet know.
Shiraishi? Shiraishi!
It appears you are similar.
Not like him.
They lost!
Please return them.
Guess I got no choice.
Well, at least for a little while...
...I can play rough.
I did it!
Why, though?
To put it plainly...
They're my friends.
He does not stop to worry.
He is not like us. He does not choose.
Ah, maybe it's because he has a different decision to make.
It isn't about whether to worry or not.
We're fundamentally different from him.
Do you think you can change your nature so easily?
My nature?
No, it's difficult to put into words.
So I'll word it the difficult way.
HE'S!
INGENIOUS!
YOU'RE!
HORRIBLE!
TALENTLESS!
Listen, Shiraishi! He's not telling the truth!
Before this debate can continue, you must consider that question.
I have worried about this myself.
I long to be free of it.
Anything more than this...
I don't have the capacity for.
The biggest loss yet.
You lose
Give them back!
Will you just give up?!
I don't get it at all!
That's fine.
I know...
And I've made my choice.
I was told to protect everyone...
And I've decided to protect them!
I don't care anymore.
Ahem... It's me, Shaberryman.
Right now, Yuz-Yuz is asking, "Why?"
"Why would Rookie go this far?"
Surely, you all at home
already know that much.
It's determination, of course.
However, there's one thing you all don't get.
It's about Yuz-Yuz who has, up to this point, lived freely and done whatever she wanted to without being arrested.
SHABERRYMAN
It's something we all relate to, and something the new guy, Hatena, tries to emulate.
Furthermore, Dogengers has no numbering convention.
We don't number our additional seasons,
like "Dogengers 2" or "Dogengers 3."
And if this were "Dogengers
4," people may say,
"Oh, if I don't watch it all, I
won't be able to keep up!"
We're trying to make our story more easily accessible.
Eh, I'll just cut to the point. Even though this isn't a direct sequel, we're building up to something...
In other words, those dolls...
My...
Bye-bye.
...precious friends!
Tanaka! Are you okay?
Man.
...are his friends from way-back-when!
Here!
Let's go!
Welcome back...
C'mon, get up!
W-wait!
Idolls!
I'm sorry!
I'm so, so sorry!
I...
We know already.
She almost flew into a rage when we got stolen.
And why shouldn't I have?!
But...
We promised...
...that we'd watch over you.
I'm sorry!
Hey, don't cry.
Yeah, really...
Don't cry!
I'm sorry.
Wow, you're just full of apologies!
It's... alright.
Hey! Stop ignoring me!
Well...
You didn't...
...tell us to wait!
Let's go!
Idoll!
Aww man, stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
So loud.
Reminds me of someone I know!
- Who're you talking about?!
- C'mon, don't fight!
- I didn't mean anything by it!
Whatever!
Bye-bye!
Wait!
But there's more!
There's him.
The result appears that even Yuz-Yuz would have trouble against those three.
And their next task is to find a new target. Namely, me.
The choice I must make...
Is to retreat.
Well then, shall we continue
your suffering later,
You and I?
This is for you.
Hyakutoban!
Pleased to meet you!
You okay?
Yeah...
I'm okay!
Looks like he got away.
- But surely next time we'll—
- I think...!
I should inspect the scene of the crime.
You all go home without me!
B-but...
Quickly. I'll be alright!
Well, if you need help with anything—
I'll be alright!
C'mon, y'all!
Sure...
Take care!
See you!
And then?
Well actually, Ohgaman snored really loud!
Hey, don't tell him that!
I'm just saying what happened!
He might get mad, though!
So pretty...
Tanaka?
It's nothing...
You were always...
...watching over me, but...
I wasn't able to do the same.
So...
I'm so sorry—
No...
Don't talk like that.
Man...
Thank you.
That's too tight!
There, there...
Shiraishi? Shiraishi!
Do you copy?
Shiraishi!
I...
...wasn't suited to any of this.
Hey, keep it together, Shiraishi.
I...
Shiraishi!
I don't think I can...
...be a real hero.
So, Akuta...
About that...
We need to talk.
How To Raise Your Rookie!
Chapter 7: If Your Subordinate Says "We
Need To Talk", That's Bad News!
Next Episode
Hi, everyone~!
I'm a manager too, so I understand.
Subordinates saying "We need to talk..." is seriously wack!
Next time: "The Crime Of Stealing Your Heart"
Episode 9
The Crime Of Stealing
Your Heart
Shiraishi—!!
Idolls... Welcome back! (We're crying a lot)