Oh, yeah!
Not on my watch!
Maid Butler...
My apologies for not writing.
Yes, long time no see.
This is all that kid's fault...
Utterly so.
GAAAH!
Is the Secret Society of Darkness...
Finally bankrupt?
There are still a few options left.
The heroes can no longer move freely.
-Huh?
-Why?
"Hero activity..."
"New regulations?!"
That new order has gone into effect.
- Hmn?
-For real?
And surely, these new options...
Will open up even more decisions and choices for us.
That time I met all you guys, right?
SP110-Px was developed by the police department to perform special operations.
Its name: Special Agent Hyakutoban!
I won't run away anymore! I'll never give up!
We'll support each other again and again
I'll protect this metropolis, for the future I want to believe in
Swear to give me the praise I need to grow! Dogengers!
The dream I saw that day will someday come true
Yes, if I find the strength to surpass my days of being timid
To shine brighter than the wimp I knew myself to be
Like a beacon telling me not to forget my mission
Anyone can pretend to be tough, like a stubborn machine
And when we realize that, we can find friends!
There's an APB on you: you are wanted!
Because your dreams are not fictional
I want to be a hero just like you
I won't run away anymore! I'll never give up!
We'll support each other again and again
I'll protect this metropolis, for the future I want to believe in
Swear to give me the praise I need to grow! Dogengers!
Uh...
We would like to hear it
in detail once more.
It won't change no matter
how many times I say it.
It's simple.
You are to cease vigilantism at once. That's all.
All such activities within the jurisdiction of our constitutional government shall be taken over...
by Hyakutouban.
As for the rest of you...
As you have each individually done until now...
Go back to your public relations work.
I... don't get it...
In other words,
it says, “Don't fight.”
Now you got it.
Thanks to you all,
this man's popularity?
Has gone up wonderfully.
Now, he can take over for you all.
- You expect us to just give you a "Yes Sir" and walk away?!
- If you have a problem...
...Take it up with the mayor.
But...
Just calm down and think veeeeery carefully.
Now that nearly the entire Secret Society of Darkness has been apprehended...
All that's left is for Yuz-Yuz
...to be found and put behind bars!
Ah...
It's as I said earlier.
Thanks to you all?
He's grown up a bit.
He's become someone you can rely on to do this.
Chief...
Regulations aside...
When it comes to Yuz-Yu-
We are...
Humanity's heroes.
Now then.
All you “real heroes...”
What do we do?
It's alright!
Please leave everything to me!
Shiraishi?
Why not?
Please, fight in my place.
-Hey!
-Big bro...
O-of course, I don't want to
fight without you all...
First things first,
if I don't produce results,
the higher-ups won't listen to change.
That's just the kind of organization the police is.
That's the unfortunate reality of it.
- But...
- Chief.
Huh?
I'll become a true hero.
Shiraishi...
Let's go, Mr. Akuta.
Right.
Everyone!
Once again...
It's thanks to you all that
I could become who I am now.
Into Special Agent Hyakutoban...
Shiraishi...
I'll see you soon!
Are we really okay with this?
Huh?
Did anyone notice something different?
▮▯▯?
This thing...
Says that.
Hey, gramps.
What t'do... oh?
Um...
Don't try anything pointless.
Kosaka's younger brother told us everything.
About Yuz-Yuz.
She's a threat to this entire city.
But...
I have a problem.
Yuz-Yuz is a good kid.
I think she just can't tell the difference between right and wrong.
-You think they'll forgive her?!
The police?
Sir...
I'm an officer too.
I'm not here to pass judgment...
But to help people!
Well said.
Well, I have a good mentor.
You'll have to introduce me sometime.
Who do you think I'm talking about?
Who knows...
Acting like you don't know...
Hm?
Eh?
Ah!
Looks like a win.
I can use this.
Oof! Ah, that's it!
So,
-Shiraishi, right?
-Yes, yes.
“Remember everything you've
been through up to now!”
Ah, is that so?
He said that!
Got it, right?
I remembered all my data!
And then...
I found what I really wanted!
I...
Don't want things...
I want people!
A-ha!
Even though you're a thing?
The reason you've never fit in in this town...
Is because you're a thing.
So you don't need that thing called hope.
Wanting things is what you're made for.
Scissors are only good for cutting paper.
It's the same case.
So, if we're clear...
I'm expecting great things from you.
H-Have conviction! I've been running so much my feet are tired anyway.
I'll leave it to you!
Everyone!
Incident-in-progress.
Where?
Komenoyama Observatory.
It sounds like Yuz-Yuz.
Shiraishi.
Right.
Listen.
I'm worried about their recent movements.
Hyakutoban... requesting suppor-
So this was his plan?
So this...
Shabberyman did it!
Alright, we're heading home!
Yeah!
All members of the Secret Society of Darkness have escaped. Requesting immediate...
And which option shall he...
...choose?
Shiraishi.
I'm going to arrest the entire
Secret Society of Darkness.
I'm sure Yuz-Yuz...
Will be fine.
That's a kick! I don't like
doing it, but it's a kick!
And this is a punch!
That's Galia's weakness!
Aaah, that's so great! This is it!
Aight, going back! Work's waiting!
Work's waiting for us! That way, right?
Ah, it's been so long since I've
seen him in a good mood.
Was that directed at me?
Rude.
Let's go break something.
Ho!
So that's your choice?
Oh, I see! I understand now!
Her time to make her choice...
...has not yet been chosen!
Hm?
You're under arrest for several blatant violations of the law.
Oh?
By your pitiful self...?
Ya got the guts to take all of us on?
All of us?
Yes.
I'm...
Here we come.
Shiraishi.
YOU'RE UNDER AREST!!!
I'll do it!
For my seniors...
...For everyone!
This just in; The Secret Society of Darkness has escaped from prison.
According to police sources, Special Agent Hyakutouban is currently engaging them.
This is good.
This is very good.
You think this is "good?"
Shiraishi!
Mr. Akuta!
Get back up!
Get the support out of here!
Absolutely not!
Please... sir!
I have to fulfill my promise to everyone...
Please leave everything to me!
Let me protect them this time!
Hey, hey, hey, what are you doing?
Bring them in!
Am apologies about this.
Here we go!
Shiraishi!
I-I'm alright!
From here on out...
I'm counting on you to speak your mind.
That promise...
We made...
I'll keep it!
That's why...
I...
Won't die!
Understood!
I'm alright!
I'll protect everyone!
I'm...
A true...
Shiraishi!!!
Ah.
You've certainly become a true hero.
-Hey! You okay?
-Are you alright?
AAAAAAAAAH!
They did it...
They did it!
Hey. They defied the order.
Arrest them all now!
No, there's something else...
What?!
Breaking news!
Regarding the new "hero activity" regulations. The mayor has issued a major revision.
Said changes go into effect immediately.
- As of now...
- Let's get you out of the way.
Here.
Next up, today's weather!
They can't have... they really can't have...
They actually took it to the mayor?!
Mayor of Fukuoka, Souichirou Takashima
Big bang.
Yahoo, this is the-whaa?
So you'll be next?
Hey, get outta here!
When Sekikaguo grows, its size increases by more than would be allowed even for a National Strategic Special Zone.
This relaxation of Civil Aeronautics Law was my reward...
For focusing on my PR work.
Go back to your public relations work.
You seriously have the money for this?
Of course I do.
This is the first time I've bought something like this.
It's so coooool!
Let's go!
Today I have a health lesson for you: ensure that you properly take your medicine...
AND SLEEP!
-All washed up?
-I washed them! I washed them!
As long as I have my kale juice...
The end draws near!
Got ya!
You didn't even drink it.
Alright! Looks like I'll teach PE!
Doing it properly!
While having fun!
Learn to move your body the right way!
This is the proper form!
PE!
Farm to table pizza, delivered straight to you!
I'm hungry!
Good point.
Pizza Cooc!!
Your backyard is the best source for food!
There are many ways to eat mentaiko!
Here, have my recipe book!
This all seems pretty ordinary.
He says, “good luck everyone!”
I'll go for SNS--
Huh? What's this kind of quality is this?!
I guess I shouldn't litter.
At this time, this president's book...
Uh... I don't get it at all!
Are you picky eaters?
Ensuring a balanced diet is vital!
That's what dietary education's about!
Oh, Shadow likes it, dont'cha?
They're certainly an interesting bunch.
You understand what's interesting?
They're not talking about...
Supporting you.
Cool, huh?
I've got something to say,
so let me say it.
So get this, Shiraishi...
They all support...
People who can't manage on their own.
Even I won't do so at this point.
Relying on people and letting them rely on you...
That's support.
That's...
Becoming comrades.
That's support?
Brother!
Right!
Ex!
Calm down, everyone!
That's enough!
One, t-
Right!
Hey, wait!
It's true.
I was wrong.
I...
Was being supported by everyone!
EVERYONE!
THE REST!
IS UP TO YOU!
They supported me...
So, now it's my turn.
What's this thing for?
Wrong.
This wasn't what I wanted.
This thin -Bye b -this th -don't w
-don't w -Bye bye Bye bye Bye -So sad..
Even though you're a thing?
Thanks for your hard day's work
You're an officer protecting the city
Handsome guys love black vinegar
Riding through nature on a trike
I want a gas-fired pizza oven
One more slice! So good! One more slice!
And if you're too fashionable, try interior design!
Thanks for all that you do! We're so grateful
You've arrested all of our troubles
You're an orthodox hero, with willpower like a steel beam!
Your apartment's so popular online
But if it goes too viral, we'll say "gomentaiko"!
Let's take our medicine and sleep for a healthy tomorrow!
And we'll meet again with a smile
We'll protect you! - The Dogengers
It'll be alright! I'm sure it'll be alright!
Dogengers: Metropolice's finale:
"Support"
Thank you, Shiraishi!
I love you!